Jhal
you should study
he says that I have requested my heart there are
some things which we do not do to be equal
like I do not leave office early
otherwise people will say that she was a girl and has gone away there is
this rumour in Punjab
do it
or not
quiz on
[sangeet]
but from 350
areas she can never go back to school
thinking about this I study a little more every inch of the way
what happened I should not miss my father that is why
sometimes I make up mother's Mohan Bhagwat Katha
[sangeet] I
fulfil Rajesh's wish only because
[sangeet]
Shivratri festival Pranav tells
us to fight for the world instead of the other part remembering this that
when you do a little more to be equal then you should
do more too
milk ashwagandha and rectangle from this plane
promise yourself that you will definitely improve your standards
ICICI Lombard wish you happy
birthday do it
to Ajay